Privacy Policy
==============

Who we are?
-----------

The website BCA – Best Casinos Australia, accessible via the URL [https://best-casinos-australia.com/](https://best-casinos-australia.com/), is owned and operated by **Ella Wilson** under the company name BCA – Best Casinos Australia. Our commitment to maintaining the privacy of our website’s visitors is a chief concern for us.

Scope of the Privacy Policy: This Privacy Policy details the types of personal information that are gathered and logged by **BCA** Best Casinos Australia and the ways in which it is used. Please note that this policy is exclusively applicable to our online operations and to the personal information shared and/or collected on the Best Casinos Australia website. It does not extend to data that is compiled offline or through channels other than this website.

For further clarifications or inquiries about our Privacy Policy, please get in touch with us directly.

**What type of information has been collected**
-----------------------------------------------

The company collects two types of information from the site: “personal information” and “non-personal information”.

**Non-personal information**
----------------------------

The information is mainly gathered by utilizing analytical cookies from third-party sources like Google Analytics. This is done to enhance the standard of our services and preserve an excellent user experience. The data obtained is broad and covers various aspects, including but not restricted to the pages browsed, duration of stay on specific pages, time of access, type of browser and operating system used on your device, online browsing activities, clicks, and language preference.

**Personal information**
------------------------

When you browse the website, there are various types of data we may obtain from you, which may include but not be restricted to your IP address, contact details, email address, as well as additional details like your areas of interest and personal preferences.

**Data You Give to Us**
-----------------------

No personal details are required to access this website, however, you will need to register your email address if you’d like to join our mailing list. This subscription entitles you to receive exclusive information about promotions, bonuses, bets and more! You can easily opt out of the service at any time by clicking the ‘unsubscribe’ link at the bottom of any email we send. Alternatively, you can reach out to us via email, text message or phone call and we’ll be happy to help – a record of our conversation may be kept for security purposes.

**Information We Obtain Automatically**
---------------------------------------

Every time you come to our website, it’s like a digital handshake; our system obtains information from you – like your IP address, location, the date and time of your visit, the pages you view, your computer operating system and browser info – plus any device settings specific to you. All this data creates a unique picture of your online presence.

**What We Do with Your Personal Information**
---------------------------------------------

We understand how important your personal information is and take great care in safeguarding it. That’s why we only use it for the purpose of providing you with the best possible experience. We won’t share, rent, or sell your personal data to any third parties – ever! Your trust is our top priority, so rest assured that we’ll handle your information with the utmost care.

Third Party Privacy Policies
----------------------------

**best-casinos-australia.com** Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### **Purposes For Which We Will Use Your Personal Data**

It’s essential to be aware of how your personal information is going to be used when you entrust it to a company or organization. Here we take the protection of your data very seriously. We’ll share with you the reasons why we need and use your personal details.

**What We Won’t Do with Your Personal Information**
---------------------------------------------------

We understand that when you entrust us with your personal information, it’s a big deal. That’s why we thought it was important to use this blog post to provide a clear picture of what we will never do with your data. Your privacy is our priority and we take it seriously.

**General Account Registration Policy**
---------------------------------------

You have the option to join the Site and create a free account, though it’s not a requirement to participate in promotions unless otherwise stated. Unfortunately, visitors under the age of 18 (or the equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction) are not able to register an account. We have no intention of collecting any personal information from children and visitors below this age. If you ever decide that you would like to delete or de-activate your account, we will retain your registered information for statistical and analytical purposes as outlined in our Privacy Policy.

### **Protection of Children**

The Site is a gambling information portal, and we take the wellbeing of younger users very seriously. We do not accept any visitors under the age of 18 – or the equivalent minimum age in their jurisdiction – nor do we knowingly solicit or collect data from them. If we discover accidentally that we have done so, we remove their personal information from our records as soon as possible. We hold ourselves accountable for the actions taken by minors on our platform, and as such take great care to ensure our content is suitable for all age groups, including in our outbound marketing campaigns such as email newsletters.

**What are your rights?**
-------------------------

Certain situations may entitle you to certain rights regarding your personal data under data protection laws which include:

No fees will be charged when you request access to your personal information, or exercise any other rights. However, if your requests are excessive, repetitive, or clearly unfounded, we may impose a reasonable fee for compliance or decline to honour your request.

### **How long we keep your personal data?**

We take data privacy and security very seriously. We only collect, store and use the personal data that you provide us for as long as necessary to fulfil our commitments under our agreement with you and to comply with applicable legal obligations. This means that your personal data will be kept for the duration of our contractual relationship or until you request its deletion or until any relevant statutory retention periods expire, whichever is shorter. If your personal data are no longer required for any of these purposes, we will delete it in a secure manner.

If you decide to shut down your User Account, we will instantly remove all your data except for what is legally necessary to safeguard. In certain cases, we may anonymise your information so it cannot be associated with you anymore and use it for research or statistical purposes without further notifying you.

CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)
---------------------------------------------------------

Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:

Request that a business that collects a consumer’s personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.

Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.

Request that a business that sells a consumer’s personal data, not sell the consumer’s personal data.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

GDPR Data Protection Rights
---------------------------

We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.

The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.

The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.

The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.

If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.

**Responsible gambling and our services**
-----------------------------------------

We take responsible gambling seriously and strive to provide an environment that puts the safety of players first. With this in mind, we have designed and implemented a variety of services to ensure that all players are gaming responsibly.

First, we provide comprehensive resources about problem gambling, including reliable facts and information on diagnosis, prevention, treatment options and other related issues. Our website also features a Responsible Gambling section with important information on how to keep gaming safe and enjoyable.

We also utilize industry-leading technologies which not only protect player accounts but also track their wagering behavior for warning signs of irresponsible or problematic play. This allows us to proactively intervene when necessary and inform players if their activity needs to be adjusted in order to remain responsible.  Additionally, our customer service representatives can answer questions about responsible gambling practices as well as help any customers who may express concerns over their own behavior regarding our services. 

Finally, we work hard behind the scenes with governments around the world in order to promote legislation which encourages responsible gambling practices by all members of society; this includes strict minimum age requirements as well as regular inspection procedures for all operators within any given jurisdiction.    It means that both players and operators alike can be held accountable for ensuring a safe playing environment where everyone has access to appropriate resources regarding problem gaming awareness and prevention—something which is deeply embedded into our core values.

Changes to This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
----------

**Email**: [\[email protected\]](https://best-casinos-australia.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
